搞什么啊
Fucking hell.
好的 我们开始吧
All right, let's go.
现在是凌晨4点
It's 4:00 a.m.
对 我们凌晨4点开始
Yeah. We start at 4:00 a.m.
我以为你是开玩笑
I thought you were joking.
那怎么会是开玩笑
How is that a joke?
因为是凌晨4点
'Cause it's 4:00 a.m.
我们凌晨4点开始 这样每天 你可以进行三次健身 而不是两次
We start at 4:00, so you can do three workouts a day instead of two.
好的 但现在是凌晨4点
Okay, but it's 4:00 a.m.
你到底想不想超越扎瓦
Do you wanna be better than Zava or not?
我们要怎么看清东西 天还是黑的
Well, how are we gonna see? It's dark out.
搞什么鬼啊
Fucking hell.
去穿衣服 否则我会弹你的睾丸
Now get dressed. Or I start flicking your balls.
你真变态
This is perverse.
(必威)
(西汉姆对里士满)
哎哟
Whoops.
好的
There you go.
(泰德 谢谢你为我做的一切 内森)
早安 靓女蓝精灵
Good morning, Sassy Smurf.
早安 万宝路男
Good morning, Marlboro Man.
你知道 你整晚都在打鼾
You know, you snored all night.
很抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
没事 其实挺令人安心的
That's all right. It's actually very soothing.
像大海的声音
Sounded like the sea.
很高兴你没听到船鸣笛的声音
Well, I'm glad you didn't hear any boat horns,
鉴于我昨晚吃了那么多炸山药
given all the fried yams I ate last night.
嘿 我在想 我们在一起总是很开心 对吧
Hey, I was thinking. We have a good time together, yeah?
泰德 是的 人称其为“同时高潮”
They're called simultaneous orgasms, Ted, yes.
对 但我的意思是
Yeah, well, but I mean
还有聊天 说笑这些 对吗
also all the talking and laughing and all that stuff. Yeah?
当然 除了你那些恼人的双关语
Sure. Well, apart from all your dreadful puns.
是 是很难
Right. Well, it's tough.
有时就在嘴边 我不得不说出来 你懂吗
Sometimes I just see 'em there, and I gotta take a swing at 'em, you know?
不 我...我的意思是
No, I-- Well, what I'm getting at is...
我在想 也许...
Well, I was just thinking maybe...
我们可以找天来次真正的约会
we could go on an actual date sometime.
你和我 我们一起
You know? You and me, together.
天啊 不要
God, no.
我很感谢你仔细考虑了再回答
Well, I appreciate you taking the time to consider it.
泰德 我们不能约会
Ted, we can't date.
为什么
Why not?
-你生活一团乱麻 -我一团乱
- You're a mess. - I'm a mess?
当然了
Course you are.
我也是一团乱麻 但我的这一团 比你进度超前了三年
I'm a mess too, but I'm a mess three years further on than you,
所以我现在只是一丝乱麻
so I'm more of a slight disarray.
要我说 你是一丝明媚美好的乱麻
More like a slight disarray of sunshine, if you ask me.
天啊
Oh, God.
-抱歉 -泰德 我前任再婚那天
- Sorry. - Ted, on the day my ex got remarried,
我用吸管喝了一瓶红酒
I drank a bottle of red wine through a straw
告诉优步司机说我爱上他了
and told my Uber driver I was in love with him.
然后 他送我到家时 我吐个不停
Then, when he dropped me home, I puked so much,
嘴巴就像《闪灵》里那台电梯
my mouth was like an elevator from the goddamn Shining.
我的评分被降到了3.9
Knocked my rating down to a 3.9.
3.9
3.9?
去你的 干吗这个语气 你是多少
Fuck you. Why? What's yours?
天啊 你是五星乘客 对吗
Oh, God, you're a five, aren't you?
你当然是五星 你怎么拿到五星的
Course you're a five. How the fuck are you a five?
不知道 我干净整洁 我说 “请你”和“谢谢你”
I don't know. I'm tidy. I say "Please" and "Thank you."
有时他们看起来很累的话 我会提出我来开车
Sometimes I offer to drive if they look tired.
你真是一团乱麻
You are such a mess.
泰德 我喜欢我们现在的状态
Ted, I like our status.
炮友关系 就像 娜塔莉波特曼和艾什顿库奇
Friends with benefits, like Natalie Portman and Ashton Kutcher.
不 我觉得你想的是2011年另一部
No. I think you're thinking of 2011's other
“好友变成偶尔的床友”浪漫喜剧
good-friends-turned-casual-lovers based rom-com.
《爱情无线牵》
No Strings Attached.
《朋友也上床》是 米拉库尼斯和贾斯汀汀布莱克
Friends with Benefits was Mila Kunis and Justin Timberlake.
天啊 2011年朋友们都忙着上床啊
Wow. 2011, friends be fuckin'.
是
Yeah.
那么 让我们活在2011年 轻松又自在
So, let's keep things 2011. Cool and breezy.
宛如阿拉伯之春
Like an Arab Spring.
祝你们这周末对战西汉姆好运
And good luck against West Ham this weekend.
鲁伯特去死吧
Fuck Rupert
他好意思称为“蛋蛋”的 皱皮口袋也可以去死
and that shriveled raisin-pouch he calls a nutsack.
你好 是弗洛叫的
Hello! Here for Flo?
-你可以上车 亲爱的 -太好了 谢谢
- You can jump in, love. - Lovely, thank you.
真不错 灰色车座 谢谢
This is nice. Gray seats? Yes, please.
...西汉姆 这是真正的机会
...West Ham. This is the real opportunity
奇迹小子可以从此化身为奇迹男人
for the Wonder Kid to become the Wonder Man...
101.
100.
Ninety-nine.
你为什么睡觉只穿上衣
Why do you only sleep with a top on?
因为我上身冷 下身热
Because I get cold upstairs and hot downstairs.
我懂
I get that.
早啊
Mornin'.
足球教练
第三季第四集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
你听听鲁伯特在这里是怎么说的
Listen to what Rupert said in this one.
“我真的很期待再次见到我的旧俱乐部
"I truly look forward to seeing my old club again.
里士满是一流的球队”
Richmond are top-class."
-真是个软骨头的废材 -谢谢你
- What a soggy, wet piece of shit. - Thank you.
是 我去训练场了 再次感谢你给我这个机会
Right, I'm off to the training ground. Thanks again for the opportunity.
宝贝 这是你应得的
Babe, you earned it.
珊迪和我想出了 一个超级好玩的伴伴营销点子
Shandy came up with this super fun Bantr promo.
要用上球队所有单身球员
It uses all the single players on the team.
对
Yeah.
你在“伴伴”的匿名男子也许是 一位职业足球员
The anonymous man you're Bantr-ing with could be a professional footballer.
真棒啊
That's great.
你是说所有单身球员都参与
And that's all the single players, you say?
所以是科林 丹尼 山姆等等
So, it's, like, Colin and Dani and Sam, et cetera?
对 但山姆好像不会再参与了
Yeah, although I don't think Sam's doing it anymore.
-不会 -真好玩
- No. - So fun.
-琼斯女士 -你好 芭芭拉
- Ms. Jones. - Hello, Barbara.
-小芭 你好吗  -叫我“芭芭拉”
- All right there, Barbs? - It's "Barbara."
如果可能的话 能给我两张 里士满对西汉姆的比赛门票吗
If possible, could I get two tickets for the Richmond-West Ham match?
杰克这周末可能会来伦敦
Jack might be coming to London this weekend.
没问题
Of course.
杰克是谁
Who's Jack?
杰克丹弗斯
Jack Danvers.
给你公司融资的风投老板
The head of the VC that funded your company.
我们的上司
Our boss.
是 那个杰克啊 当然了
Yes. That Jack. Of course.
没问题 芭芭拉
That's not a problem, Barbara.
我可以给你在我的包厢留几个座位
I can let you have some seats in my suite.
真好
Lovely.
瑞贝卡 太感谢你了 你这么做真好心 而且很高效
Thank you so much, Rebecca. That's so kind of you and so efficient.
基莉
Keeley.
谢谢 芭芭拉
Thanks, Barbara.
我们对战西汉姆时 一定要避开的战术就是伪九号
So, the one thing we cannot do against West Ham is the False Nine.
-因为那是内特的专长 -没错
- 'Cause that's Nate's shit. - Exactly.
所以我们决定用经典的4-4-2
So, we decided to go with our classic 4-4-2.
那混蛋肯定是这么预期的
Which is exactly what that prick expects us to do.
所以我们反着来 五个前锋 全面攻击
So, we do the opposite. Five up front. Full-on attack.
但是内特知道我们会这么做
But Nate knows we're gonna do that,
因为内特知道我们想要 像他那样思考 来跑赢他的思维
because Nate knows that we're trying to outthink him by thinking like him.
别管内特了 别管思维了 也别管苏格拉底了
Well, fuck Nate, fuck thinking and fuck fucking Socrates.
我们得停止像内特那样思考 而是思考一下
So, we gotta stop thinking like Nate and start thinking
如果内特像我们一样思考 他会认为我们会怎么思考
like Nate would think we would think if Nate were thinking like us,
采用我们代入内特的思维 去思考我们的思维
and then do the last thing that Nate thinking like us
而他像这样的我们一样思考时 最不可能采用的战术
thinking like Nate thinking like us would ever expect us to do.
把扎瓦放到后场 用内特的伪九号战术
Have Zava drop back and play Nate's False Nine.
便是如此
Voi-fucking-là.
高明
Brilliant.
-主要是彼尔德的想法 -不 这是集体的智慧
- It's mostly Beard's idea. - Nah, it was a group effort.
我有个问题
I do have one question.
-当然 -谁在乎啊
- Of course. - Who fucking cares?
你们觉得扎瓦会同意吗
Do you think Zava'll do it?
该死
Fuck!
-早安 -嗨
- Good mornin'. - Hey.
-不好 发生什么了  -罗伊觉得我们无法战胜内特
- Uh-oh, what's wrong? - Roy doesn't think we can beat Nate.
-希金斯也这么认为 -彼尔德先对我说的
- Higgins doesn't think so either! - Beard said it to me first.
-你背刺我啊 你怎么敢... -今早你到这里...
- You throw me under the bus? How dare-- - You walked in here this morning--
-你要出卖我  -停...
- You're gonna sell me out? - Whoa! Whoa.
你们互相指责的样子 比象头神给人指路时更忙啊
Y'all pointin' more fingers than Ganesha givin' directions.
听我说 你们几个得冷静下来 亲吻和好
Now look, you fellas need to calm down and just kiss.
他说得对
He's right.
保持简单 天才们
Keep it simple, smartypants.
船到桥头自然直 别担心
An answer will show up. Don't worry.
但在那之前 我有个问题要问你们大家 我是一团乱麻吗
But until it does, here's a question for y'all: Am I a mess?
靓女昨晚和我一起过...
Sassy ended up spending the night last night and--
不 安静 头条不是这个
No, hush your butts. That ain't the headline.
我今早问她要不要来次真正的约会
Well, I asked her out on a proper date this morning.
她无情地拒绝了 她说我是... 原话是“一团乱麻”
She turned me down cold. She said I was-- and I quote-- "a mess."
-对 -听上去是钻石狗开会时间
- Yeah. - Sounds like a case for the Diamond Dogs!
放出猎狗
Release the hounds.
对 来吧 开始
Yeah, here we go! Let's do it.
老天
Fuck's sakes.
是
Yes.
-“是”什么  -是 你是一团乱麻
-"Yes" what? - Yes, you're a mess.
好的 请阐释
Okay. Expound.
我们这周要对战内特
We're playing Nate this week,
而你的表现像是这没什么大不了
and you're acting like it's not a big deal.
一切如常 仿佛他没伤害你
Nothing's different. He didn't hurt you.
嘿 我们现在不聊内特
Hey, look, we ain't talking about Nate right now.
我是问你们我是不是一团乱麻 好吗
I'm asking you if you think I'm a mess. All right?
小希希 你怎么看
Higgy pie, what do you think?
我觉得我不明白你为什么不生内特的气
I think I don't understand how you're not pissed off with Nate.
我们共同依赖症匿名互助会上 常常说到这句话
We have a saying in Co-Dependents Anonymous.
-是...什么  -简逼我和她一起去
- Y-- What? - Jane makes me go with her.
对
Yeah.
痛苦如同一氧化碳
Pain is like carbon monoxide.
向伤害了你的人 表达痛苦就像是打开通风口
Expressing it to the person who hurt you is like opening a vent,
但是憋在心里只会毒害自己
but holding it in will poison you.
我喜欢这说法 但内特没有伤害我
I like that. But Nate didn't hurt me.
胡说
Bullshit!
罗伊 你想加入钻石狗的讨论吗
Roy, did you wanna get in on this Diamond Dog situation?
-嘿 罗伊 嘿 罗伊 -嘿 罗伊 来
- Hey, Roy! Hey, Roy. - Hey, Roy. Here, Roy.
来 罗伊 来这里嘛
Here, Roy. Come here, Roy.
啦...
La, la, la, la, la!
(英超联赛 一周概要)
本周最瞩目的比赛显然是里士满对西汉姆
So, the match of the week is clearly Richmond and West Ham.
两支球队都经历了强势的赛季初
Now, it's been a strong start to the season for both of these teams,
但我认为在伦敦德比中 铁锤帮是热门
but I think the Hammers are favorites, going into the London derby,
基于奇迹小子内森谢利精妙的战术能力
based on the tactical acumen of the Wonder Kid, Nathan Shelley.
对 谢利很厉害 这毫无疑问
Yeah, Shelley is brilliant, there's no doubt about that,
但是扎瓦是天才 这个原因让我看好灰狗
but Zava, he is a genius. I like the Greyhounds for this one.
是我的兄弟
That's my guy!
不 他不属于你 他是我的
No, you can't have him. He's mine.
-我们继续说周日的... -嘿 各位 快看
- Let's move on, shall we, to Sunday's-- - Hey, look. Guys, guys.
谁在乎啊
Who cares, right?
快点 我们还有活要干 来吧
Now come on, we've got work to do. Let's go.
他说得对
He is correct.
我们必须无视这些电视人 就算他们支持我们
We must ignore these talking faces. Even when they are in our favor.
谢谢你 “佐罗”
Thank you, "Zorro."
没错 但是 其实念“佐豪”
Exactly, but it's actually pronounced "Zoreaux."
为什么
Why?
我不知道 可能因为 我父母就是这么叫我的
I don't know. Because that's how my parents say it, I guess?
朋友 你想怎么叫自己就怎么叫
My friend, you can be whoever you want to be.
我的所有孩子到了七岁时 我允许他们给自己起名
I let all of my children name themselves once they reach the age of seven.
所以我最大的孩子名叫“蠢蛋”
That is why my eldest is called "Smingus Dingus."
要有鸿鹄之志 也许理想就会实现
Dream big, and you may never wake up.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊
Jesus.
我不敢相信我要这么说 但是嘿 各位 我同意扎瓦
I can't believe I'm about to say this, but hey, lads, I agree with Zava.
对 这是超级重要的一场比赛 但我们只需要专心踢球 做该做的事
Yes, it's a big fucking game, but we've just gotta focus, do what we do,
-懂我的意思吗  -是 他是对的
- do you know what I mean? - Yeah. He's right.
还有 别忘了
And don't forget, yeah?
-相信“相信” -对
- Believe in "Believe." - Yes.
搞什...
What the--
什么
What?
-见鬼 -怎么了
- Oh, shit. - What?
(坚信胜利)
-你干吗那么做  -我只是想看看
- Why the fuck did you do that? - I was just checking
我是否获得了将东西砍为两段的能力
if I acquired the ability to chop things in half.
是 如果你能呢
Yeah, and what if you had?
抱歉 哥们 我没想清楚
Sorry, bruv. I didn't think it through.
大伙 有人把这个撕成两半了
Fellas. Someone ripped this in half.
怎么回事 什么
What the fuck? What?
怎么回事
What the fuck?
开玩笑吧
You're joking
怎么回事
What the fuck?
你好
Hello...
玉
Jade.
(伦敦西汉姆联 必威)
内森
Nathan.
谢利
Shelley.
很高兴再见到你
Lovely to see you again.
好吧
Okay.
抱歉我最近没常来
Sorry I've not been around much.
你没有吗
You haven't?
对...我最近很忙 忙我的新工作
No. No, I've been really busy with my new job.
十分重要的新工作导致我很忙
Big new job just keeping me very busy.
听起来挺蠢的 也许你应该辞掉 你重要 忙碌的新工作
Sounds silly. Maybe you should quit your big new busy job.
总之 我是来拿外卖的
Anyway, just here to pick up my takeaway.
我为我的所有员工买了午餐
I bought lunch for my whole staff.
除了训练员 因为他们食量如牛
Apart from the trainers, 'cause they eat like cows.
抱歉 这话有点...不是 他们很可...我是说 他们很可爱
Sorry, that sounds-- No, they're love-- I mean, they're lovely people.
他们是素食者
They're just vegetarians.
(雅典品味)
不是吧
No way.
看看谁大驾光临了 我没看错吧
Look who's here. No fucking way!
-你知道这是谁吗  -杰森杰里
- Do you know who this is? - Jason Jelly.
-对 -不对 是“内森谢利”
- That's right. - No, "Nathan Shelley."
对 内森谢利
That's right, Nathan Shelley,
西汉姆联的经理 光临我的餐厅
manager of West Ham United, in my restaurant!
-重要的一周啊 伙计 -是
- Big week, my guy. - Yep.
太重要了 我是戴瑞克 我是这里的经理
Big fucking week. I'm Derek. I'm the manager here.
需要什么尽管说
Anything you need, you got it.
-好的 -经理之间互相关照
- Okay. - From one manager to another.
是 其实不太一样 但...
Yeah, well, it's not quite the same, but--
这周要对战你的旧球队
Facing your team this week.
这是来真的 对吧
That's gotta be hard-core, right?
你在媒体上说了他们好多坏话
I mean, you talked a lot of shit about them in the press.
-对吧 我喜欢 -抱歉 我能买单吗
- Didn't ya? I loved it. - Sorry, can I pay?
不 这顿算我的 我请 好吗
No. This is on me, okay? On me. Understand?
这位先生在这里不用花钱
This man's money is no good here.
永远别让他花钱 除非是买酒 酒钱必须付啊
Never charge. Except for booze. Gotta charge for booze.
我没订酒 现在是12点30分
I didn't order any booze. It's 12:30.
打趴他们 铁锤帮加油
Knock 'em dead. Go Hammers!
难以置信 喂 知道这是谁吗
No way. Oi, do you know who this is?
好的 拜拜
All right, okay. Bye.
卡
And cut!
很不错 科林 谢谢你
Lovely, Colin. Thank you.
好 下一个是丹尼
All right. Okay, Dani, you're up.
我非常紧张
I'm very nervous.
不 不用紧张 坐在这里就好 看向镜头
No. Don't be nervous. Look, just sit here. Look into the camera
假装你在和老朋友聊天
and pretend you're talking to an old friend.
我最老的朋友是哈维尔
My oldest friend is Javiar.
很好 你认识哈维尔多久了
Great. How long have you known Javiar?
几个月 但他下周就108岁了
Only a couple of months, but he turns 108 years old next week.
-就是他了 -是
- Perfect. - Yeah.
最后检查
Final checks.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你好 基莉 -嗨
- Hello, Keeley. - Hi.
对 稍微向左边挪一点
Yeah. Just scoot to your left a little bit.
对 很好 开始吧 丹尼
Yeah, that's it. Okay, off you go, Dani.
(伴伴 你永远想不到...)
你也许不知道我是谁 但我觉得女人最美丽的部分
You may not know who I am, but I think the most beautiful parts of a woman
是她的缺点
are her flaws.
卡 谢谢 丹尼 下一位
And cut! Thank you, Dani. Next!
好的
Okay.
-给你带了咖啡 -是
- Brought you coffee. - Yeah.
-顺利吗  -天啊 太顺利了
- How's it going? - Oh, my God. This is great.
-是吗  -他们好出色
- Yeah? - They're great.
我只是...好爱当老大
I just-- I love being the boss.
-为此干杯 是 -干杯
- Cheers to that. Yeah. - Cheers to that.
佐豪 你准备好了吗
You ready, Zoreaux?
是 但其实我现在叫“范达美”
Yeah, but I actually go by "Van Damme" now.
行 很好 开始 范达美
Okay, great. Action, Van Damme.
你不知道我是谁
You don't know who I am,
但我在找一位喜欢在沙滩简短散步的人
but I'm looking for someone who likes short walks on the beach,
这样我们可以把更多时间用来...
so we can spend more time, you know...
卡
And cut.
太好了 谢谢 范达美 下一位
Great, thanks, Van Damme. Next!
-范达美  -对 我的新名字
- Van Damme? - Yeah. It's my new name.
很酷 为什么
Cool. Why?
因为我爱尚格云顿范达美
Because I love Jean-Claude Van Damme,
扎瓦说我想怎么叫自己都行
and Zava told me I should be whoever I wanna be.
-好的 酷 -好的 范达美
- Okay, yeah. Cool. - All right, Van Damme.
-回见 兄弟们 -回见
- All right, boys. - Take it easy.
他好性感
He's so fucking hot.
-他的背景是什么  -杰米 他很自大的
- What's his story? - Jamie? He's so cocky.
但我想到了这个高度 你必须自大
But I guess you have to be at this level.
但他只在乎自己
But he only thinks about himself.
至少他以前是
At least, he used to.
开玩笑的 不是
Joking. No.
但他不为自己的行为 和给别人造成的后果承担责任
But he's not accountable for his actions and what they do to others.
他道歉的功夫倒是越来越好了
Except he is getting better at making apologies.
但是他只用下半身思考
Still, he only thinks with his dick.
不过我觉得他好久没和人交往过了
And yet, I don't think he's seen anyone in ages.
我只是想知道我能否和他睡 宝贝
I just wanna know if I can bang him, babe.
不知道呢
I don't know.
你大概问他比较合适 毕竟是他的老二
You should probably ask him, it's his dick.
很好 可以了 杰米
Cool. Off you go, Jamie.
你们怎么还在这
What are y'all still doing here?
教练 你最好看看这个
Coach, you're gonna wanna watch this.
是那种视频吗
Is it one of them videos
参军的家长在服役很久后回家
of a military parent coming home after a long tour?
如果是的话 我晚餐就要 喝自己的眼泪和鼻涕了
'Cause if so, I'm gonna be eating tears and snot for dinner.
不是
Not quite.
(摄像头1 更衣室)
来了
Here we go.
(摄像头1 经理办公室)
这是哪来的
Where'd this come from?
这位神人想到调出安保监控录像
This fucking legend thought to pull the security footage
当我们告诉他标志的事时
when we told him about the sign.
我想你可以让一个人退出记者行业
I guess you can take the boy out of journalism
但你永远无法抹杀他内心的记者
but you can't take journalism out of the boy.
是 你把气氛搞砸了 重点是
Right, you fucking ruined it now. The point is,
我们寻找的答案揭晓了
the answer we were looking for has arrived.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
这样的视频也许能激励球队
A video like this could motivate a team, perhaps.
特伦特 谢谢你的帮忙
Thank you for your help, Trent.
希望有天年轻的罗伯特瑞福德 会在电影里扮演你
May a young Robert Redford portray you in a film someday.
可能是达斯汀霍夫曼
Probably Dustin Hoffman.
-晚安 -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
回家吧 两位 好好休息
Go home, guys. Get some sleep.
好的
Okay.
-晚安 泰德 晚安 彼尔德 -晚安
- Good night, Ted. Night, Beard. - Good night.
晚安 教练
Night, Coach.
教练
Coach.
我之前在想你的靓女困境
I was thinking about your Sassy situation.
是
Yeah.
简的姐妹来了
Jane's sister is in town.
-不用了 教练 谢谢 -这是正确答案
- No, thank you, Coach. - That's the right answer.
(《独立日报》 拉索对奇迹小子)
挑灯夜战啊
Burning the midnight oil, I see.
对 抱歉闪到你了
Yeah. Sorry for the smell.
被“灯”闪到
The oil burning.
你对这周末有信心吗
So, you're feeling confident about this weekend?
是 对 我觉得有
Yeah, no, I think so.
对 是的 我们会摧毁敌方 对吗
Yeah, no. Go-- Yeah. We're gonna destroy, right?
很好
Good.
不 只是 我...
No, it's just, I--
我离开后没见过泰德
I just haven't seen Ted since I left and...
我们算是不欢而散
We didn't leave on the best of terms and...
我觉得我欠他一句道歉
I feel like I owe him an apology or something.
你做了对你来说最好的决定
You did what was best for you.
你还能怎么样
What were you meant to do?
留在球队 一辈子支持泰德
Hang around, supporting Ted for the rest of your life?
我想还是算了吧
I don't think so.
你没做错任何事 内森 我保证
You've done nothing wrong, Nathan, I promise you.
这份工作是你赢得的
You earned this job.
那我见到他时该说什么
Well, so what do I say when I see him?
什么都不用说 除了“你好”
You say nothing, apart from "hello."
你直视他的眼睛 你和他握手
You look him in the eye. You shake his hand.
然后你打败他
And then you beat him.
然后我们去庆祝
And then we go and celebrate.
好的
Okay.
晚安 内森
Good night, Nathan.
晚安 鲁伯特 谢谢你
Good night, Rupert. Thank you.
曼尼昂先生
Mr. Mannion.
(米歇尔:你的比赛 在这里上了头条 祝你好运)
(一定很精彩 谢谢你的分享)
(雅克布医生)
(下周三10点下次咨询见)
嘿
Hey.
上夜班 还是在摸鱼
Working late? Or hardly working?
梗好像没说对
Well, I don't think that's how the joke goes.
什么梗
What joke?
不用放在心上 你好吗
Never mind. What's up?
我真的很想赢这场比赛
I really want to win this one.
我知道
I know.
一切都好吗
Everything okay?
我是一团乱麻吗
Am I a mess?
当然了 所以我们才这么合拍
Of course you are. That's why we get along.
我也希望能让你别管靓女说什么 但她通常是对的
And I wish I could tell you to ignore Sass, but she's usually right.
看来靓女已经告诉你... 当然了 闺蜜谈话
So, Sassy already told you about the-- Of course. Girl talk.
闺蜜谈话
Girl talk.
那么 一切都好吗
So, is everything all right?
是 我很好
Yeah, I'm good.
俄克拉荷马
Oklahoma?
我是“一团正在变好的乱麻”
I'm a work in "progmess."
晚安 泰德
Good night, Ted.
你已经赢了 你明白的吧
You already won, you know?
你把那家伙赶出了你的人生
You got that turkey out of your life.
打败他们
Beat them.
晚安 老大
Good night, boss.
(西汉姆联)
(铁人们 加油)
(AFC里士满)
哎 我看起来精神吗
Oi, do I look all right?
当然 为什么这么问
Of course you do. Why?
如果杰克真的出现
Well, if Jack actually shows up,
我希望他认为我看起来神秘而强大
I want him to think that I look mysterious and powerful.
充满活力 你知道吗
Dynamic, you know?
-所有这些 -你很神秘 强大 充满活力
- All of that. - You are mysterious, powerful and dynamic.
糟糕 我好紧张
Shit, I'm nervous.
我得去重新画唇线
I think I need to go and reapply my lip liner.
-我们在楼上包厢见 -好的
- I'll see you upstairs in the suite. - Yep.
嗨 瑞贝卡
Hey, Rebecca!
-鲁伯特 -见到你真好
- Rupert. - Wonderful to see you.
-贝克丝 新发型真美 -嗨
- Bex. Love the new hair. - Hi.
我没换发型
I haven't changed my hair.
你也不该换 现在就很完美
Nor should you. It's perfection.
小家伙怎么样
So, how's the little one?
对 黛安 她已经会走路了 你能相信吗
Oh, yeah, Diane. She's already walking. Can you believe that?
是 在房子里到处流口水和便便
Yeah. Drooling and pooing around the house.
有其父必有其女啊
Takes after her father.
嘿 今天对我们手下留情啊
Well. Hey, take it easy on us today.
这我不能打包票
No promises.
该死
Oh, shit.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我这里有点情况
I've got a bit of a situation here.
谢谢 但其实不是这个
Thank you. But it's actually not that.
你真是救命恩人
You're a lifesaver!
我通常很准时的
Usually I'm like clockwork,
但因为最近压力太大了 月经提前来了
but because I've been so stressed, I've come on early.
真高兴这是超大码而不是小码的
I'm so happy that it's a super and not a skinny.
小码的到底谁会买啊
Who are those even for?
我的阴道又不是在节食 我可是来月经了
It's not like my vagina is on a diet, I'm on my fucking period.
哎 谢谢你的帮忙
Oi, thanks for helping me.
还有 我爱你的鞋子
And I love your shoes!
-是 谢谢 送人玫瑰嘛 -是
- Yeah. Thanks. Pay it forward. - Yeah.
抱歉 不好意思
Sorry. Excuse me.
嗨
Hi.
天 你好高
Boy, you're tall.
你的爸爸是一棵树吗
Is your dad a tree or something?
没 我只是在逗乐子
No, I'm screwing around.
嘿 说到树 你们今天站哪队啊
Hey, speaking of trees, who are y'all rooting for today?
西汉姆
West Ham.
是 很合理 对
Yeah, no, that makes sense. Yeah.
你们先 对 我还要下一层楼
Go ahead. Yeah. Going down one more floor.
-谢谢 -是 不客气
- Thank you. - Yeah, of course.
祝你好运
Best of luck out there.
嘿 内特 是你吗
Hey, Nate. That you?
嗨 我没看见你
Hi. I didn't see you there.
-没关系 哥们 你好吗  -是 我很好
- That's okay. How you been, man? - Yeah, okay.
是 那就好
Yeah. Good.
听着 泰德
Listen, Ted.
我只想说 我离开的方式...
I just wanna say that the way I left--
内森 你在这里啊
Nathan. There you are.
是
Yeah.
(西汉姆联 铁器越强)
(西汉姆联 炉火越猛)
嘿 鲁伯特
Hey, Rupert.
-泰德 -很高兴又见面了
- Ted. - Nice to see you again.
祝你好运
Good luck.
-基莉 是 -她出色极了
- Keeley? Yeah. - She's absolutely fantastic.
她来了
Here she is now.
-嘿 对 -基莉 这位是杰克丹弗斯
- Hey. Yeah. - Keeley? This is Jack Danvers.
你好
Hello.
我好像有东西在你那里
I believe you have something of mine.
要命 你是杰克
Oh, fuck. You're Jack?
这有点难堪
This is a bit embarrassing.
-不 -对 我们都以为你是男人
- No. - Yeah. We all thought you were a man.
对 还有这个啦
Yeah, that too.
那谜语是怎么说的来着
It's like that old riddle.
-什么谜语  -这个很棘手的
- What riddle? - You know, always a tricky one, this one.
一对父子出了车祸
A father and son are in a car wreck.
爸爸当场死了 儿子被送到急救室
Dad dies instantly, the son is rushed to an emergency room.
手术医生走进来 说道
A surgeon walks in and says,
“我不能给这个男孩做手术 他是我的儿子”
"I can't operate on this boy. He's my son."
怎么可能
How is it possible?
-因为她是个女人 -她是同性恋
- Because she's a woman. - She's gay.
-捐精者 -他处在模拟宇宙里
- Sperm donor. - He lives in a simulation?
对 我想这个谜语也有点过时了
Right. Yeah, I guess that's a bit dated now.
那么 我猜“杰克”是“杰奎琳”的昵称
So, I assume "Jack" is short for "Jacqueline," right?
不 是我父亲想要男孩的意思
No. It's short for my father wanted a boy.
我去外面坐坐哈 现在去
I'm gonna go and sit down now, outside. Now.
杰克 欢迎你
Jack, welcome.
我们不能带饮料入座
We are not allowed to take drinks to our seats.
所以如果你想喝得大醉酩酊 那我们最好现在开喝
So if you want to get plastered, we should probably do that now.
好的
Okay.
你先
Well, after you.
瑞贝卡 你真幽默
You're so funny, Rebecca.
芭芭拉迷上瑞贝卡了
Barbara's obsessed with Rebecca.
我希望她不会试图杀了她 然后把她的皮肤做成西服来穿
I hope she doesn't try and kill her and wear her skin as a suit.
搞什么
What the fuck?
干杯 今天会很美好
Cheers. It's gonna be a good day.
-好了 巴兹 -哎
- All right, Baz. - Oi!
这里是里士满球迷酒吧
This is a Richmond pub.
没事的 梅 他是我朋友
It's all right, Mae. He's with me.
滚出去
Get the fuck out!
加油 里士满
Come on, Richmond!
加油 里士满...
Come on, Richmond! Come on, Richmond!
今天座无虚席 大家都来看
It's a full house for today's battle
西汉姆联和扎瓦效力的AFC里士满对战
between West Ham United and Zava's AFC Richmond.
这场胜利会让任一球队跃至联赛头位
A win would take either team to the top spot in the table,
挤下榜首的强旅曼城队
knocking mighty Manchester City off number one.
克里斯 这应是场 难分伯仲的比赛 有何预测
Should be a tight match, Chris. Any predictions?
我已经不做预测了 阿尔洛
I stopped making predictions, Arlo.
因为我从没猜错过
Because I was never wrong.
以至于我开始担心是我造成的结局
Got to the point I was worried I was the one making things happen.
真有意思
Well, that's interesting.
我知道你会这么说
I knew you'd say that.
他们消逝和死去
They fade and die
好运无处寻
Fortune's always hiding
我找遍各地
I've looked everywhere
我一直在吹泡泡
I'm forever blowing bubbles
空中的美丽泡泡
Pretty bubbles in the air
西汉姆联...
United! United!
内特
Nate.
我们今天享受过程吧
Let's have fun out there today, yeah?
西汉姆联心情不错 拥抱压力
West Ham are quite happy to just soak up the pressure.
面对里士满 不冒任何险
Not taking any risks at all against Richmond,
在主场迎战这支球队
of all teams, at home.
-也是里士满长足进步的证明 -没事 我们没事
- A sign of how far Richmond have come. - It's all right. We're okay.
扎瓦真是大威胁
What a threat Zava is.
里士满 右边 跟紧 别怕
Richmond! To the right! Tight! Don't get scared.
依然无比无 多亏了佐豪精彩的救球
And it stays nil-nil, thanks to an amazing save by Zoreaux.
-范达美 -范达美
- Van Damme. - Van Damme!
听说他现在希望被称为“范达美”
I hear he wants to be called "Van Damme" now.
为什么
Why?
很可能得去他的童年找答案了
Well, we'd probably have to dive into his childhood for that answer.
里士满需要关键的传球 才能打破铁锤帮的防守
Richmond need the key pass to unlock the Hammers' defense.
也许就是这一球
That could be the one.
-塔特射中横梁 -不
- Tartt hits the woodwork. - No!
-差一点啊 -扎瓦没有人防
- That was close. - Zava was wide open.
给扎瓦
For Zava!
上半场还有两分钟 这场伦敦德比
There'll be two more minutes in the first half of this scoreless,
无人得分 但扣人心弦
but pulsating, London derby.
-奥比桑亚拿到球 -不
- Obisanya caught in possession. - No.
西汉姆突然发动进攻
And here come West Ham on the break.
阿尔曼多接近球门
Armando bearing down on goal.
-好耶 -好
- Yeah! - Yes!
进了 就在范达美眼皮底下
And it's there. Right under Van Damme.
这位加拿大的守门员显然不像
The Canadian keeper apparently not as unstoppable
与他同名的布鲁塞尔肌肉男一般无敌
as the Muscles from Brussels.
这话不公平 阿尔洛 没有人能比得上他
That's not fair, Arlo. Nobody is.
-我们有经验的 加油 -加油 小伙子们
- We've been here before. Come on. - Come on, lads.
就在中场休息前 铁锤帮1比无领先
The Hammers go up 1-nil just before halftime.
该死的
Fuck it.
好了 各位 加油 拿出实力来结束上半场
All right, guys. Come on, now. Let's end this half strong!
围过来
Huddle.
(队长)
这是干什么
What's this shit?
不知道
I don't know.
-低一点 正确方向 五 -高明
- Lower. Move it right. Five. - Brilliant.
-现在 来吧 五 -裁判 快吹哨
- Right now, come on. Five. - Ref, just blow the fucking whistle.
西汉姆施压了
West Ham pressing now.
-不 -上半场结束前几秒
- No. - A new tactic from the Hammers
铁锤帮发动新战术
in the closing seconds of the first half.
阿尔洛 任何时候开始改变都不晚
It's never too late to change, Arlo.
-不 -该死 去你的 该死的
- No! - Fuck! Fuck you! Fuck!
现在是2比无 天啊
And it's 2-nil. Oh, deary me.
不好意思
Excuse me.
这是怎么发生的
How did that happen?
中场休息
We go to halftime.
里士满一直控球
Richmond have dominated possession,
但突然之间 铁锤帮就2比无领先
but out of absolutely nowhere, it's 2-nil to the Hammers.
我们应该有更好的成绩
We don't deserve that.
刚是发生了什么
What the fuck just happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
嘿 各位 我一会儿就回来 好吗
Hey, fellas. I'll be right back. Okay?
你要去哪
The fuck are you going?
-很快的 好吗  -我们要和球队说什么
- I'll just be a minute or two, okay? - What do we tell the team?
不知道 给我个惊喜
I don't know. Surprise me.
嘿 老大 你下来做什么
Hey, boss. What you doing down here?
我只想告诉你 泰德 我相信你
I just wanted to tell you that I believe in you, Ted.
是
Uh-huh?
我知道最近我给你很大的压力
And I know that I've been putting an awful lot of pressure on you
要在今天赢球 但我只是希望你忘掉那一切
to win today, but I just want you to forget all about that.
就做你自己 享受过程
Just be yourself and have fun.
-好的 -是
- Okay. - Yeah.
好的 谢谢你
Okay. Well, thank you.
我相信你 泰德
I believe in you, Ted.
气氛好凝重
And it's intense.
-我得走了 就这样 -你去忙吧
- I better go. All right. - Off you pop.
记住 享受过程
Remember, have fun!
对 好兴奋啊
Yes! This is so exciting!
不
No.
这就是你们的惊喜 是吧
This is your surprise, huh?
一分钟前他们失魂落魄的 看看他们现在
A minute ago, they were catatonic. Now look at them.
-他们准备好大战一番了 -说实话 泰德 有时这是好事
- They're killers. - Frankly, Ted, sometimes that's good.
(这是世界舞台)
天啊 走出隧道的里士满
Oh, my. Richmond coming out of the tunnel
虎视眈眈 充满敌意
with a palpable chip on their shoulder.
天啊 球场上气氛真的紧张起来 我觉得下半场一定精彩无比
Wow. A real tension on the pitch. I think we're in for an exciting half.
下半场开始 里士满想要强势开头
We begin the second half with Richmond looking for a strong start.
-加油啊 杀了他们 -杀了他们
- Come on, boys. Fucking kill 'em. - Fucking kill 'em.
-来吧 -杀
- Here we go! - Kill!
这个铲断很糟
That's an awful tackle.
-他如果只吃个黄牌... -该死
- He would be fortunate to escape... - Oh, fuck.
就算走运了
...with just a yellow.
这张红牌合情合理 里士满
It's a deserved red, and Richmond
下半场大部分时间将只有十位球员上场
will play almost the entire second half with ten men.
其实他是个很友善的年轻人
He's actually a very sweet young man.
西汉姆发起进攻
Here come West Ham.
范达美现在被罚下场了
And now Van Damme has been sent off.
-我们踢得像意大利球队似的 -就是啊
- We're playing like Italians. - I know.
棒极了
It's awesome.
老天
Oh, dear.
场上有点剑拔弩张了
It's getting a touch spicy out there.
阿尔洛 剑拔弩张 应该说是枪炮齐上阵
Spicy, Arlo? This is vintage vindaloo.
不
No.
蒙特劳失去理智了 里士满失去了第三位球员
Montlaur has lost his mind, and Richmond have lost a third player.
逗我呢吧
Fucking come on.
里士满完全失控了
Richmond have completely lost the plot.
扎瓦一定在想自己做了什么 被困在这样的局面里
Zava must be wondering what he's done to deserve this.
(下半场 西汉姆联4 里士满1)
好
Yes!
4比1 铁锤帮获胜
And it's 4-1 to the Hammers.
这场比赛从不相伯仲变成了天平一边倒
It went from evenly matched to unevenly matched
然后演化为点燃一罐汽油的混乱
to light a match on fire and put it into a can of petrol.
下半场应该附带可能引起不适的警告
That second half should've come with a trigger warning.
扎瓦的非凡进球 也没有减轻观看这场比赛的痛苦
One extraordinary goal by Zava did not make it any less tough to watch.
里士满展现了我们前所未见的一面
Richmond showed a side of themselves we've never seen before.
他们踢得愤怒 卑鄙和丑陋
They played angry, dirty and ugly.
这也是扎瓦最小的三个孩子的名字
Which are also the names of Zava's three youngest kids.
要命
Shit.
-嘿 没事的 -要命
- Hey, it's okay. - Shit.
你们看得开心吗
Did you guys have fun?
是
Yeah.
暴力挺有娱乐性的 对吧 从某方面来说
The violence was quite entertaining, wasn't it? In a way.
罚范达美下场是个错误
Sending off Van Damme was a mistake.
他充满激情
He played with passion.
“激情”这种词是用来形容爱的
"Passion" is a word we use when we talk about love.
也是用来形容犯罪的
It is also a word we use to describe a crime.
有时也是一种水果
Sometimes it is also a fruit.
天啊 真抱歉
Oh, gosh. I'm so sorry.
(主席包厢)
-我们搞砸了 -我们矫枉过正 带着恨意踢球
- We fucked up. - We overcorrected and played with hate.
-希望你可以吼吼我们 -拜托了
- Be great if you yelled at us a bit. - Please.
-骂我们是坨屎什么的 -现在就骂
- Call us pieces of shit or something. - Now.
你可以揍我们
You can hit us.
把这事儿翻篇
Get it over with.
试了新的方法 不奏效 没什么大不了
Tried something new. It didn't work. Big whoop.
但是那个U盘在你们谁那里 给我吧
I will take that thumb drive one of y'all's got.
忘了这事吧 两位 赛季还有很多场比赛
Shake it off, fellas. Lot of football left this season.
-真是个混蛋 -没错
- What a fucking arsehole. - I know.
赢了这场比赛 你一定感到很开心吧
You have to feel pretty good about yourself after that win, yeah?
是 里士满显然被扰乱了
Well, yeah. Richmond were clearly rattled.
说实话 赢得比我想象中容易
It was easier than I expected, if I'm honest.
泰德呢
What about Ted?
比赛结束时不和他握手 有点自大啊
Quite a snub not to shake his hand at the end of the game.
我没握手吗 我不是故意的
Did I not? I didn't mean to.
我...也许我当时太激动了
I-- Guess I just got caught up in the excitement of it all. Yeah.
失陪一下 我...
Excuse me a minute. I just...
谢利教练 曼尼昂先生让我给你这个
Coach Shelley, Mr. Mannion asked me to give you this.
(骨头与蜜糖 贵宾通行证)
他一小时后和你在那里见面
He'll meet you there in an hour.
谢...
Thank--
-瑞贝卡 见到你真好 -贝克丝 彼此彼此
- It's so good to see you, Rebecca. - You too, Bex.
瑞贝卡 亲爱的
Oh, Rebecca, my dear.
-很遗憾你输球了 -谢谢
- So sorry for your loss. - Thank you.
走吧 老头 你的睡觉时间早过了
Come on, old man. It's way past your bedtime.
见到你很开心
Lovely to see you.
我看到你和你的助理在一起了
I saw you with your assistant.
你的女儿不应承受这个 贝克丝也是
Your daughter deserves better, and so does Bex.
别再到处乱搞了
Stop fucking around.
你的
Here you go.
我们通常表现好得多 也友善得多
We are normally a lot better than that. And nicer.
球队得到的红牌比进球多 这谁都不想看到 对吧
Well, it's never great when your team gets more red cards than goals, is it?
是的
No.
真是一场闹剧
What a shit show.
总之 好消息 伴伴上热搜了
Anyway, good news. Bantr's trending.
-真的吗  -对
- It is? - Yeah.
肯定和自我简介页面的变动有关
Pretty sure the change to the bio line helped.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
(伴伴 想和有钱的名人睡吗 )
是谁改的
Who did this?
我 今天下午我上载视频时改的
I did. This afternoon, when I uploaded the vids.
不用谢
You're welcome.
-珊迪 -对
- Shandy. - Yeah.
这和伴伴的初衷背道相驰了
This is the opposite of what Bantr is trying to do.
你开玩笑呢 大家会爱死的
Are you joking? They're gonna love it.
他们的订阅人数一小时内翻了三倍
I've literally tripled their subscribers in an hour.
你得改回去 立即 拜托
You need to change this back, now. Please.
是
Yeah.
很高兴认识你
It was really lovely to meet you.
-彼此彼此 -不好意思
- You too. - Excuse me.
嘿 他来了
Hey. Here he is!
传说中的奇迹小子
The Wonder Kid himself.
今天的英雄
The man of the hour!
曼尼昂先生 谢谢你
Thank you very much, Mr. Mannion.
拜托 叫我“鲁伯特”
Please, no. "Rupert."
内森
Nathan.
谢谢 卡克斯女士 那...
Thanks, Ms. Kakes. That's...
内森 这位是安娜斯塔西亚
And Nathan, allow me to introduce Anastasia.
铁粉
Huge fan.
天啊 你很有名
Oh, my God. You're famous.
你也是
So are you.
恭喜你的胜利
Congratulations to your victory.
是的 谢谢
Yeah. Thank you.
塔特 快点 晚餐前再来一次
Come on, Tartt! One more before dinner!
走吧 教练
Let's go, Coach.
看得真痛苦啊
That was hard to watch.
提埃里 西汉姆今日控制全场 看到泰德拉索面对
Thierry, West Ham's domination today saw Ted Lasso being totally exposed
前助理内特谢利 束手无策
by his former assistant Nate Shelley.
盖瑞 我喜欢中国哲学家老子的一句话
Gary, I love this quote from a Chinese philosopher, Laozi,
“当学生准备好时 老师就会出现
"When the student is ready, the teacher will appear.
当学生真正准备好时 老师就该退场了”
When the student is truly ready, the teacher will disappear."
灰狗们
The Greyhounds...
-嗨 泰德 -嗨
- Hi, Ted. - Hey.
比赛的事很遗憾
Sorry about the match.
不 没事 今天是一场苦战
No. That's all right. It was a tough one.
亨利不在 他去参加生日派对了
Henry's not here right now. He's at a birthday party,
-但我会... -不 没事
- but I'll-- - No, that's okay.
我其实只是想和你聊聊 你现在有空吗
I was actually hoping just to chat with you. You got a minute?
当然 一切还好吗
Sure. Is everything okay?
是的 这个...不好 你知道 我只是...
Yeah. Well-- No. You know, I just...
我想简短地说一点事
I wanted to say something real quick.
听着 我...
Look, I...
我知道你和我已经分开了
I know that you and I aren't, you know, together anymore.
而我尊重这点
And I respect that. Okay? I do.
但是 你知道
But, Well, you know,
你和雅克布医生的事让我不太舒服
this whole thing with you and Dr. Jacob really ticks me off.
在你们开始前 我们没有真正聊过这件事
And I'm upset that we didn't ever really get to talk about it
这让我感到不开心
before it all started.
是
Yeah.
听着 我明白 我说这些话
And look, I understand that me saying all this,
也许是不对的 但是...
might be the wrong thing to do, but...
我只觉得如果不说
I just feel like not saying it...
那并不是...
isn't the...
那也不对
Well, wouldn't be the right thing either.
因为我们要一起养育这个男孩 对吗
'Cause we gotta raise this little boy together, you know?
我们摆脱不了彼此 我们会有共同的孙辈
We're stuck with each other. We're gonna share grandkids.
我爱你 米歇尔
I love you, Michelle.
我爱亨利
And I love Henry.
我爱我们的家
And I love our family.
无论是什么样的家
No matter what it looks like.
好吗
Okay?
当然
Of course.
我晚点再找你们聊
Well, I'll talk to y'all soon.
晚安 告诉亨利我爱他
Have a good night. Tell Henry I love him.
晚安 泰德
Good night, Ted.
(纪念格兰特瓦尔)
字幕翻译:易晗